Two young doctors with a dream of making it big... Really big!
Breast Men is a tv movie, drama, comedy film directed by Lawrence O'Neil.
We follow the two Texas doctors who invented the modern
breast implant and its surgical procedure.
However, when success and money come their way, they
split up and follow different paths.
One becomes the surgeon of the everyday woman while the other's career
freefalls and has to settle with strippers and actresses.
The film covers their history and their
inventions, from the sixties until today.
Dr. Kevin Saunders, played by David Schwimmer.
Dr. William Larson, played by Chris Cooper.
Laura Pierson, played by Emily Procter.
Gerald Krzemien, played by Matt Frewer.
Hersch Lawyer, played by Terry O'Quinn.
Timmi-Jean Lindsey, played by Kathleen Wilhoite.
Breast Men is a 1997 American semibiographical dark comedy-drama television film
written by John Stockwell and directed by Lawrence O'Neil for HBO.
The film explores themes of surgeon, plastic surgery, stripper, breast.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.